**How to help: [Hurricane Helene](https://www.fidelitycharitable.org/guidance/disaster-relief/how-to-help-hurricane-helene.html) and [Hurricane Milton](https://www.fidelitycharitable.org/guidance/disaster-relief/how-to-help-hurricane-milton.html) guidance**

**Time is running out to make tax-deductible contributions in 2024. Review our year-end [contribution guidelines](https://www.fidelitycharitable.org/giving-account/what-you-can-donate/charitable-year-end-tax-deadlines.html).**

Please enter a search term

Please enter a search term

Privacy Policy
==============

* * *

This privacy policy is applicable to donors and individuals visiting this website or otherwise interacting with the Fidelity Investments Charitable Gift Fund (“Fidelity Charitable”) directly or through its service provider National Charitable Services LLC, a Fidelity Investments company (“NCS”). If you represent a company, advisor or non-profit entity that has a business relationship with Fidelity Charitable or National Charitable Services, please see the [National Charitable Services privacy policy](https://www.fidelitycharitable.org/legal/ncs-privacy-policy.html) to learn more about its privacy practices.

Our commitment to privacy
-------------------------

Since our establishment in 1991, Fidelity Charitable has recognized the importance of maintaining the confidentiality, integrity, and security of personal information about our current and potential donors. When you provide personal information to Fidelity Charitable, we believe that you should be aware of our policies designed to protect the privacy of this information and how we use it to service a Giving Account.

As used in this privacy policy, personal information means information about an individual that is collected and maintained in carrying out our activities, and by which the individual can be identiﬁed. Please note that information by which an individual cannot be identiﬁed (for example, anonymous, de-identified, or aggregate information) is not considered personal information and therefore is not subject to this policy.

We hope you will take a moment to review our privacy policy, including certain aspects that depend on whether you deal with us directly or through a financial advisor or authorized representative.

How and why we obtain personal information
------------------------------------------

Fidelity Charitable recognizes the importance of maintaining personal information about you, and when we use it, we do so with respect for your privacy. We obtain and use personal information about you to service, maintain, and protect your Giving Account; process transactions in your Giving Account; respond to inquiries from you or your representative; develop, oﬀer, and deliver charitable giving programs and services; operate and carry out our activities; and fulﬁll legal and regulatory requirements. Fidelity Charitable collects public and non-public personal information from customers and visitors from various sources. Some examples include:

* You or your representative on applications or forms (for example, when you interact with us via phone or on the web, or when you visit our websites or use our applications)
* You or your representative regarding your preferences (for example, your choice of electronic statement delivery)
* Transactional activity in your Giving Account (for example, contributions, pool exchanges, and grant recommendations)
* Other interactions with Fidelity Charitable (for example, webinars, events, interactions with our virtual assistant, use of two factor authentication)
* Information from consumer reporting agencies (for example, for fraud prevention purposes)
*  Information from other third-party sources (for example, to verify your identity, update your contact information and to process transactions on your behalf)
* Other sources with your consent or with the consent of your representative (for example, if you contribute assets from other institutions, or if you interact with our social media services)

How we protect your information
-------------------------------

We implement and maintain physical, administrative, technical and organizational measures designed to protect personal information and we regularly adapt these controls to respond to changing requirements and advances in technology.

Privacy, security, and service online are just as critical as the rest of our operations. Fidelity Charitable works with our online systems service provider, National Charitable Services®, LLC (a Fidelity Investments company), to secure Fidelity Charitable systems from unauthorized access and to maintain the security of your online sessions. We use firewall barriers, encryption techniques and authentication procedures, among other controls, to maintain the security of your online session and to protect systems from unauthorized access.

How we share information about you with third parties
-----------------------------------------------------

Within Fidelity Charitable and among our service providers, we restrict access to personal information to those who require it to provide our services to you. For example, Fidelity Charitable has entered into a number of arrangements with Fidelity Investments® to provide investment management and administrative services to Fidelity Charitable.

Fidelity Charitable does not sell or rent donor names or information to any firm or non-profit organization. Fidelity Charitable has entered into fundraising arrangements with Fidelity Investments to offer and provide our programs to their customers. However, we do not share donor information with Fidelity Investments or any other firm or nonprofit organization for their marketing or fundraising purposes without your (or your authorized representative’s) consent. You do not have to contact us to benefit from these protections; they apply automatically to all our donors.

We may share personal information with the following entities:

* Unaffiliated service providers (for example, printing and mailing companies, securities clearinghouses, marketing service providers, and other entities who may provide services at our direction)
* Government agencies, other regulatory bodies and law enforcement officials (for example, for tax purposes or for reporting suspicious transactions)
* Other third-parties, with your consent or as directed by your representative (for example, if you request to transfer assets from another financial institution, or if you use an external aggregation website or service that you have provided permission to access your Giving Account on your behalf)
* Other third parties whose products, services and investment offerings are made available through Fidelity Charitable, and which you decide to utilize.
* Other organizations as permitted or required by law (for example for fraud prevention or to respond to a subpoena)
* In connection with corporate business transactions, such as a merger or sale of a business.

Privacy online
--------------

When you interact with us through our online channels, such as websites and mobile applications (“online channels”), Fidelity Charitable manages personal information in accordance with all of the practices and safeguards described in this policy.

When you visit Fidelity Charitable online channels, or interact with us via electronic communications, we (or our service providers on our behalf may automatically, collect technical and navigational information, such as device type, browser type, internet protocol address, pages visited, and average time spent on Fidelity Charitable online channels. We use this information for a variety of purposes, such as maintaining the security of your online session, facilitating site navigation, improving the design and functionality of our online channels and electronic communications, and personalizing your experience on Fidelity Charitable online channels. Additionally, the following policies and practices apply when you are online.

**Cookies and Similar Technologies**

We use cookies and similar technologies to support the operation of Fidelity Charitable websites. Cookies are small amounts of data that a website exchanges with a web browser or application on a visitor’s device (e.g., computer, tablet or mobile phone). Our cookies help us to collect information about visitors to Fidelity Charitable websites, including date and time of visits, pages viewed, amount of time spent on our sites, or general information about the device used to access the site. Fidelity Charitable cookies are also used for security purposes and to personalize your experience, such as customizing your screen layout.

You can refuse or delete cookies. Most browsers and mobile devices offer their own settings to manage cookies. If you refuse a cookie when on Fidelity Charitable websites, or if you delete cookies from your device, you may experience some inconvenience in your use of Fidelity Charitable websites. For example, you may not be able to sign in and access your account, or we may not be able to recognize you, your device or your online preferences.

Both Fidelity Charitable websites and third-party service providers we hire may use cookies and other technologies, such as web beacons, pixel tags or mobile device ID, in online advertising as described below. We do not share personally identifiable information about our donors with these third-party service providers, and these service providers do not collect such information on our behalf.

We may collect analytics data or use third-party analytics tools such as Google Analytics to help us measure traffic and usage trends for our online channels and to understand more about the demographics of our users.  You can learn more about Google’s practices with Google Analytics by visiting [Google’s privacy policy](https://policies.google.com/technologies/partner-sites "Page opens in a new tab"). You can also view Google’s currently available [opt-out options](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout "Page opens in a new tab").

**Advertising on Non-Fidelity Charitable websites**

Fidelity Charitable also advertises our programs and services on online channels not affiliated with Fidelity Charitable and we contract with third-party advertising companies to display these ads. These third-party advertising companies may use cookies and similar technologies to collect technical and web navigational information, such as device type, browser type, Internet protocol address and pages visited. We do not permit these companies to use information they collect on behalf of Fidelity Charitable for any purpose other than to assist them with advertising Fidelity Charitable programs.

You may opt-out of receiving interest-based advertisements from online advertising companies, including those used by Fidelity Charitable, by clicking on the AdChoices icon and following the opt-out instructions.  

If you generally want to “opt out” of receiving online interest-based advertisements on your internet browser from advertisers and third parties that participate in a self-regulatory programs like the Digital Advertising Alliance DAA program or the Network Advertising Initiative (NAI), please follow the instructions at [WebChoices: Digital Advertising Alliance's Consumer Choice Tool for Web US (aboutads.info)](https://optout.aboutads.info/?c=2&lang=EN#!%2F "Page opens in a new tab")  and [NAI Consumer Opt Out (networkadvertising.org)](https://optout.networkadvertising.org/?c=1 "Page opens in a new tab")  to place an “opt-out” cookie on your device indicating that you do not want to receive interest-based advertisements. If you want to “opt out” of receiving online interest-based advertisements on mobile devices, please follow the instructions at [YourAdChoices.com | AppChoices](https://youradchoices.com/appchoices "Page opens in a new tab")  and [Mobile Opt Out - NAI: Network Advertising Initiative (thenai.org)](https://thenai.org/opt-out/mobile-opt-out/ "Page opens in a new tab")Non-Fidelity Charitable online channels are not subject to Fidelity Charitable’s Privacy Policy. You may visit the individual sites for additional information on their privacy practices.

**Connecting with Fidelity Charitable on social media platforms**

Fidelity Charitable provides experiences on social media platforms that enable online sharing and collaboration among users who have registered to use them. We may collect information you provide by interacting with us via social media, such as photographs, opinions, or social media account ID handle. Please do not share any personal or Giving Account information via social media platforms. Any content you post, such as pictures, information, opinions, or any personal information that you make available to other participants on these social platforms, is also subject to the terms of use and privacy policies of those platforms. Please refer to them to better understand your rights and obligations with regard to such content.

**Third Party websites, online services, and content**

Our Online channels may contain links to third party websites and online services (for example, social media platforms) and may include embedded content that is hosted by third parties. This policy does not address the privacy, security, cookie policy and settings, or other practices of the third parties that provide such websites, online services, or content, and we are not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of these other websites, online services, or content providers. If you use a link to another website or online service or view third party content (for example, an embedded video), please consult the privacy policy for that website/or online service for additional information on their privacy practices and advertising opt-out instructions.

**Children's privacy** 

Fidelity Charitable’s Online channels are not directed to individuals under the age of thirteen (13). Fidelity Charitable does not intentionally collect information on Fidelity Charitable’s online channels from those we know are under 13, and we request that these individuals do not provide personal information through our online channels. If we do provide an offering that is intended to be used by individuals under the age of thirteen, it will have a separate privacy policy.

**Additional Information**

For your convenience, Fidelity Charitable offers several options for accessing and, if necessary, correcting your Giving Account information. You may review your personal information using your quarterly Giving Account Statement or by logging on to your Giving Account at [www.fidelitycharitable.org](https://www.fidelitycharitable.org/). You may also choose to write or call us with your request for information. Please see your quarterly statement for specific Internet addresses, mailing addresses and telephone numbers.

Last Reviewed October 2022

Fidelity Charitable is a 501(c)(3) public charity. We help donors maximize their generosity through our donor-advised fund, called the Giving Account. Established in 1991, we are the nation’s top grantmaker, distributing $11.8 billion to charities in 2023.

About us

Who we serve

Resources

©1998-2024 FMR LLC. All rights reserved. Portions © 1998-2024 Fidelity Investments Charitable Gift Fund. All rights reserved. _Fidelity Investments® Charitable Gift Fund is recognized as a tax-exempt public charity as described in Sections 501(c)(3), 509(a)(1), and 170(b)(1)(A)(vi) of the Internal Revenue Code._

Want more info before you open a Giving Account?

Sign up to receive occasional news, information, and tips that support smarter giving impact through a donor-advised fund.

Email: 

Please enter a valid Email

Subscribe

#### Thank You! You are on your way to making more of a difference.

Check your inbox soon for our monthly email newsletter.

* * *
